wpspeak.com 2018-04-30

# Privacy Policy - WPSpeak

We strongly believe in utmost privacy for our viewers. Our privacy policy covers all the aspects you need to consider before using our website.

## Personal Information

  * We respect the privacy of our users. At WPSpeak, the users are never asked to reveal their personal information such as race, gender, address, income etc.
  * We do not provide personal information to any third party unless required by authorities like law and order. Users should feel safe with us, take our word for it.
  * We don’t store personal information of our servers unless required for the something important for of our site.

## Use of Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.

**WPSpeak also uses Cookies including:**

  * DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

You can disable cookies through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Ads

Our advertisement partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Commission Junction
  * Clickbank
  * Kontera
  * LinkShare
  * ShareaSale
  * Other WordPress Companies and Stores

The advertisements that appear on WPSpeak are run by the above-listed ad agencies. These ad generating agencies receive your IP address by default.

WPSpeak takes no responsibility for the cookies used by third parties.
